

INFO

- 851100660
- +973 33952252
- mohamedmahfoodh85
 @gmail.com
- H: 853, R:2327, B: 523, Saar

♥ CERTIFICATES

May, 2015

Success Training Center (Enhansing Skills in Merachandising, Selling and Stock Control).

May, 2014

HABC level 2 Award in Health and Safety in the Workplace (QCF).

- March, 2012
 OSHAcademy Fire Prevention Plans course.
- Oct, 2011

ABNLP training in the Art and Science of Neuro Linguistic Programming in Customer Service.

May, 2009

Ait Centre (Comprehensive Directios in Merchandising, Selling and Stock Control.

S. MOHAMED MAHFOODH

STORE IN-CHARGE

ABOUT ME



An energatic person with strong communication and organisational skills with +10 years work experience actively seekingfor a new opportunity.

I have many qualities to bring to the work place such as good team work, organisational skills, efficiency and I am very meticulous, I show pride in all the work I do, I work well under pressure and I love a challenge. I posses excellent verbal and written communication skills and am able to relate to a wide range of people. All these skills have been enhanced during all the work experiences I have gained over the past years.

EDUCATION



2003 - 2005

Ahmed Al-Emran Secondary School Commercial

EXPERIENCE



2013 - 2018

Store In-charge | Jawad Business Group

Responsible for ensuring a consistently high standard of presentation in the store and making sure that all available space in the store is effectively utilized. Focused on maximising the customers shopping experience.

2008-2013

Customer Service | Jawad Business Group

Managing incoming calls and customer service inquiries. Generating sales leads that develop into new customers. Identifying and assessing customers' needs to achieve satisfaction.